<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Phoenix Wright | liwanag]]></title>
  <link href="http://neauro.github.io/liwanag/blog/categories/phoenix-wright/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://neauro.github.io/liwanag/"/>
  <updated>2014-01-02T21:23:00-08:00</updated>
  <id>http://neauro.github.io/liwanag/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[nadine a.]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[9 Things Re: Phoenix Wright: Dual Destinies]]></title>
    <link href="http://neauro.github.io/liwanag/blog/2013/12/23/phoenix-wright/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-23T11:03:14-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://neauro.github.io/liwanag/blog/2013/12/23/phoenix-wright</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>After NaNoWriMo finished, my pastime of choice during my commute became playing through <em>Phoenix Wright: Dual Destinies</em>. I finally finished the main story as well as the DLC the other day.</p>

<p>[ spoilers ahead ]</p>

<h2>Watching Athena fall on her face during the opening cinematic made me cringe.</h2>

<p><em>Man.</em> I was really, <em>really</em> hoping that this game wouldn&rsquo;t have another cynical dude sweatdropping at the enthusiasms of a sidekick whose an infantile woman, if not just because it&rsquo;s already done: Maya, Pearls, and Trucy <em>all</em> already play this role.</p>

<p>Fortunately, unlike the other games where women are humorous sidekicks or antagonist, Athena is a playable protag in this game, and she has her own motivations. Her main reason for entering the attourneyforce turns out to be because she wants to save a dude, Simon Blackquill — but it&rsquo;s totally platonic, and matches with her desire to save people in general, including her best friend, Juniper Woods. Hurray for friendships!</p>

<h2>Speaking of friendships,</h2>

<p>I was one of those people for whom the only redeeming quality <em>Apollo Justice</em> was the presence of Phoenix Wright himself at the end (complete with <a href="http://www.japanator.com/survey-says-just-what-on-earth-is-gap-moe--13198.phtml">gyappu moe</a>!). Coming into <em>Dual Destinies</em>, however, I was pleasantly surprised by how much I liked Apollo now, probably because he was now a familiar bro instead of an usurper.</p>

<p>I was also really happy to see both Pearls and Edgeworth gain, and the presence of the both of them in the fifth case contributed to why it was my favorite of all the ones in the game. It was just a relief to come back to the personalities that I&rsquo;ve known, and see how they&rsquo;ve changed since I&rsquo;ve seen them last. To be honest, what I wanted most out of this game was to see Maya again — and I&rsquo;m disappointed that she never showed up in person, but at the very least it was explained where she went in the first place.</p>

<h2><em>Dual Destinies</em> is also an effective example of how compelling it can be to tell the ending at the beginning.</h2>

<p>It&rsquo;s not explained why Apollo starts the game wearing a strange jacket, and later, when you realize that he was wounded in the courtroom explosion, it&rsquo;s a mystery why Apollo already has an eyepatch even before the bomb has been detonated. Skipping back and forth through time did confuse me somewhat, however, and I wish the second &ldquo;Ninetails Vale&rdquo; case had added more development of the main characters, or the world. As a standalone case it wasn&rsquo;t incredibly interesting anyway, especially since you, once again, know who the murderer is from the beginning.</p>

<h2>3</h2>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
