<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Games | liwanag]]></title>
  <link href="http://neauro.github.io/liwanag/blog/categories/games/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://neauro.github.io/liwanag/"/>
  <updated>2013-12-19T21:05:16-08:00</updated>
  <id>http://neauro.github.io/liwanag/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[nadine a.]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dragon Flight, by Next Floor]]></title>
    <link href="http://neauro.github.io/liwanag/blog/2012/09/10/dragon-flight-by-next-floor/"/>
    <updated>2012-09-10T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://neauro.github.io/liwanag/blog/2012/09/10/dragon-flight-by-next-floor</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
<div class="separator" style="clear: both; text-align: center;"><a href="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-OO6Fgnn7kNU/UE4O8ZEDLCI/AAAAAAAACag/yGjzQ0zMHrQ/s640/blogger-image-1812206283.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;"><img border="0" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-OO6Fgnn7kNU/UE4O8ZEDLCI/AAAAAAAACag/yGjzQ0zMHrQ/s640/blogger-image-1812206283.jpg" /></a></div><br />I haven't been playing iOS games recently, I guess due to a general boredom with the growing free-to-play population. The exception is <a href="http://itunes.apple.com/app/dragon-flight/id530610467?mt=8">Dragon Flight</a> by Next Floor, a simple dragon-themed shooter. Long story short: put your finger over the character, swipe left and right to eliminate rows of evil/cute monsters, collect the coins and jewels upon expelled upon monsters' expiration.<br /><br />Coins gathered mid-fray can be used to purchase increasingly expensive upgrades, which make your bullets cooler-looking and faster at killing things, which is nice. The system is clean-cut: farm dragons, upgrade to farm dragons better, farm more dragons. In the background is a high score based on how many meters you were able to cross before dying, which provides a pretty sensible long-term goal in each individual, short game. There are also power-ups you can collect mid-fray ("shoot twice as many bullets;" "become invincible and shoot forward for two seconds or so;" etc.) which mix things up a little.<br /><br />About the only bewildering thing to me is the other score system, which allots you points based on the types of dragons you killed, white dragons yielding like 100 points and tougher, yellow ones yielding 500 (or something). And sometimes when you kill a dragon a "2x" or "3x" or something pops up overhead? I'm still not sure what this means, though presumably it rewards the player for going on streaks of killing only a certain color of dragon, which is difficult to plan out when rows of randomly-arranged dragons appear and rush away in the space of seconds. I've been musing about what purpose having both a score based on "This is how far you went!" and a "This is how many points you won!" score might serve. For example, in <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tetris#Scoring">Tetris</a>,&nbsp;clearing lines as soon as possible help you stay in the game longer (and keeps your stress level low), whereas making a "tetris" or clearing four lines at once rewards more points.<br /><br />Anyway, I haven't found my answer yet, but it may be because all I care about is farming dragons (<i>give me that 8000 coin dragon egg dammit omg</i>).<br /><br />Other slightly annoying thing: placing your finger directly over the player-character to navigate her obstructs her from view, which means it can be hard to catch falling treasure. Because the screen reads movement no matter where your finger is, I experimented with navigating the player-character while holding my finger near the top of the screen, but then I couldn't see where I was shooting. I haven't thought of any possible alternatives yet for this, other than tilt-based controlling, which seems like it would be too slow for twitchy treasure-catching.<br /><br />Anyway~ Dragon Flight is a simple and satisfying time-waster, but I can't wait until I can replace it with gardening and Return to Ravnica :D</div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Awakening: The Skyward Castle]]></title>
    <link href="http://neauro.github.io/liwanag/blog/2012/09/01/awakening-skyward-castle/"/>
    <updated>2012-09-01T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://neauro.github.io/liwanag/blog/2012/09/01/awakening-skyward-castle</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
I never thought I'd actually go so far as to purchase a hidden object game instead of <a href="http://nuubu.blogspot.com/2011/09/casual-game-binge-speculation.html">just playing the demos</a>, but the Awakening series is <i>so fun</i>. I like that it has a focus mainly on puzzles (all of which always seem unique and new), and besides that the scenes are just beautiful.<br /><br /><table align="center" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="tr-caption-container" style="margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto; text-align: center;"><tbody><tr><td style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-2E48fFhY70s/UEInRHTCiCI/AAAAAAAACVU/6tO3b8Yp4Do/s1600/awakening.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"><img border="0" height="358" src="http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-2E48fFhY70s/UEInRHTCiCI/AAAAAAAACVU/6tO3b8Yp4Do/s640/awakening.jpg" width="640" /></a></td></tr><tr><td class="tr-caption" style="text-align: center;">you can't even see the particle effects floatin' around this thing, wuuuut</td></tr></tbody></table><br />Like, don't you just want to <i>be here</i>?<br /><br /><div class="separator" style="clear: both; text-align: center;"></div><table align="center" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="tr-caption-container" style="margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto; text-align: center;"><tbody><tr><td style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-VLaygD7IeAY/UEIndRF0ZqI/AAAAAAAACVk/pxOcm2Y_1uU/s1600/awakening2.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"><img border="0" height="358" src="http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-VLaygD7IeAY/UEIndRF0ZqI/AAAAAAAACVk/pxOcm2Y_1uU/s640/awakening2.jpg" width="640" /></a></td></tr><tr><td class="tr-caption" style="text-align: center;">c'mon! who could turn down a <i>flying waterfall tree</i>?</td></tr></tbody></table><br />The voice acting is a little weird, but overall Awakening is a good source of dopamine yielded by doing A to get B which is needed for C to get D for E, etc.</div>


<h2>Comments</h2>


<div class='comments'>
<div class='comment'>
<div class='author'>nadine a.</div>
<div class='content'>
I&#39;ll shoot you an e-mail :)</div>
</div>
<div class='comment'>
<div class='author'>axcho</div>
<div class='content'>
Ha! :D Now they&#39;ve got you...<br /><br />What are you working on these days, anyway?</div>
</div>
</div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some HTML5/JavaScript Links]]></title>
    <link href="http://neauro.github.io/liwanag/blog/2012/08/16/some-html5javascript-links/"/>
    <updated>2012-08-16T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://neauro.github.io/liwanag/blog/2012/08/16/some-html5javascript-links</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
Having done few HTML5 things, I've dug up some tutorials and interesting links.<br /><br /><br /><h2><a href="http://dev.opera.com/articles/view/html-5-canvas-the-basics/">HTML5 canvas - the basics</a></h2>I guess the first cool thing about HTML5 is this canvas thing, which is basically like a drawing pad that HTML5 bestows upon you, eyes glowing with love. "Go," it says. "Use this to create art with your present armory of JavaScript."<br /><br />A canvas object has a bunch of contexts, the same way a drawing pad has a lot of pages. JavaScript can be used to draw onto a context. Most browsers allow JavaScript to draw 2D things; some have experimental 3D contexts.<br /><br />Unlike a drawing pad, once you've decided to use a canvas's context, <i>that's the only context you can use for that canvas, ever</i>. It's kind of like you tore out a page from the drawing pad and all the other ones withered away in anguish.<br /><br />Interesting things canvases can do in HTML5:<br /><ul><li>draw lines, ex. <code>canvas.lineTo(xPos, yPos)</code></li><li>draw rectangles, ex. <code>canvas.fillRect(xPos,yPos,width,height)</code></li><li>draw images, ex. <code>canvas.drawImage(imgSource, xPos,yPos)</code></li><li>apply pixel manipulations to those images, ex. invert all colors</li><li>draw text (only in recent WebKit builds)</li><li>draw dropshadows and gradients for all your Web 2.0 needs</li></ul><br /><br /><h2><a href="http://html5.litten.com/understanding-save-and-restore-for-the-canvas-context/">Understanding save() and restore() for the Canvas Context</a></h2>When searching around for examples of canvas usage, I saw references to <code>canvas.save()</code> and <code>canvas.restore()</code> which were nicely explained in this article.<br /><br />In brief, every canvas contains a stack of "drawing states." Drawing states are comprised of a lot of data, including the current transformation region, the current width of line being drawn, the current front, and so on.<br /><br />If you want to draw a shape like a diamond (or rotated square), the steps to do this involve:<br /><ol><li>Make a canvas, retrieve its 2D context</li><li>2Dcontext.save()</li><li>Rotate the context</li><li>Draw a square on the context (which, since the canvas is rotated, will be diamond-shaped)</li></ol>If you then wanted to draw a new shape, like a regular square, you could easily pop the present drawing state with <code>2Dcontext.restore()</code> to get back to an un-rotated coordinate system. The diamond should stay the way that it is presently.<br /><br />Similarly, objects on a canvas can't be "just moved;" if you're translating an object across the canvas, the steps go<br /><ol><li>Clear the canvas</li><li>Draw the object in its new position</li><li>Repeat</li></ol><br /><br /><h2>HTML5: Writing a game, by Jason Croucher</h2>The blogging process of someone creating a Breakaway-type game in HTML5 and JavaScript. The final product, named Bouncing Animals, is <a href="http://jacebook.co.uk/share/html5/">here</a>. It's not really a tutorial, but I found it to be a good/simple primer.<br /><br /><ul><li><a href="http://jacebook.co.uk/blog/2010/09/11/html5-writing-a-game/">Part 1</a>&nbsp;involves: creating an HTML5 canvas, adding and drawing/playing images and sounds, how to make an event handler for a button and mouse, and starting/stopping a game.<br /><br /><table align="center" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="tr-caption-container" style="margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto; text-align: center;"><tbody><tr><td style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-3xaUG-xxqks/UCp5hUePotI/AAAAAAAACGY/eNy17Hg8YJ4/s1600/bear1.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"><img border="0" height="290" src="http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-3xaUG-xxqks/UCp5hUePotI/AAAAAAAACGY/eNy17Hg8YJ4/s400/bear1.jpg" width="400" /></a></td></tr><tr><td class="tr-caption" style="text-align: center;">getting exciting yet?</td></tr></tbody></table><br /></li><li><a href="http://jacebook.co.uk/blog/2010/09/12/html5-writing-a-game-step2/">Part 2</a>&nbsp;involves making the mushroom "wobble" between two pngs (one normal-sized, one slightly flattened) whenever it's hit by the bear.</li><li><a href="http://jacebook.co.uk/blog/2010/09/12/html5-writing-a-game-step-3/">Part 3</a>&nbsp;involves varying the bear's speed and angle.<br /><br /><table align="center" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="tr-caption-container" style="margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto; text-align: center;"><tbody><tr><td style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-dWVk26eCMu0/UCqP5OpkC1I/AAAAAAAACHQ/kv8sMErvNhs/s1600/bear2.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"><img border="0" height="232" src="http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-dWVk26eCMu0/UCqP5OpkC1I/AAAAAAAACHQ/kv8sMErvNhs/s320/bear2.jpg" width="320" /></a></td></tr><tr><td class="tr-caption" style="text-align: center;">we gettin wild in here</td></tr></tbody></table><br /></li><li><a href="http://jacebook.co.uk/blog/2010/09/15/html5-writing-a-game-step-4/">Part 4</a>&nbsp;and <a href="http://jacebook.co.uk/blog/2010/09/20/html5-writing-a-game-step-5/">Part 5</a>&nbsp;talk about game objects and optimal FPS numbers for various browsers.</li></ul><div><br /><br /><h2><a href="http://michalbe.blogspot.com/2010/09/simple-game-with-html5-canvas-part-1.html">Tutorial: Simple game with HTML5 Canvas</a></h2></div><div>An actual game tutorial for a Doodle Jump clone that's fairly comprehensive, and involves drawing objects on an HTML5 context, some animations, and so on.<br /><br /><br /><h2>JavaScript function declarations vs. function expressions</h2>In the previous tutorial, I encountered my first instance of a function expression. Essentially, a <strong>function definition</strong> looks like<br /><pre class="brush: js"> function function_name() {<br />   // stuff<br />  }<br /></pre><br />whereas a <strong>function expression</strong> looks like<br /><pre class="brush: js"> var = function function_name() {<br />   // stuff<br />  };<br /></pre></div><br />Some links I found which discussing declarations versus expressions are <a href="http://javascriptweblog.wordpress.com/2010/07/06/function-declarations-vs-function-expressions/">Function Declarations vs. Function Expressions</a> and <a href="http://kangax.github.com/nfe/">Named function expressions demystified</a>, and the differences include the following:<br /><br /><ul><li>Function expressions can be named or anonymous.</li><li>Function declarations are parsed and evaluated before any code is executed, whereas function expressions are evaluated at run-time. Therefore, if you call a declared function at any time, it should be okay, whereas function expressions must be defined before being called.</li><li>Function declarations should <i>not</i>&nbsp;be used in if-statements. In contrast, function expressions are okay to call in if-statements, and are sometimes used this way to allow for best performance ("don't define this function unless it's needed").</li><li>Function expressions mimic what JavaScript is <i>actually</i>&nbsp;doing, which is creating an object every time a function is defined.</li></ul><div><br /></div><div>In general it seems that function expressions are the favored creature.</div></div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Deluge of Recent-er News, and Some Free-to-play Chat]]></title>
    <link href="http://neauro.github.io/liwanag/blog/2012/06/22/deluge-of-recent-er-news-and-some-free/"/>
    <updated>2012-06-22T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://neauro.github.io/liwanag/blog/2012/06/22/deluge-of-recent-er-news-and-some-free</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
What have I been up to recently? Namely:<br /><br /><table align="center" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="tr-caption-container" style="margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto; text-align: center;"><tbody><tr><td style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-YYkNq4aUJU4/T9qGUiOSyGI/AAAAAAAAA1o/Y-Gt500Is48/s1600/shibacm2.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"><img border="0" height="347" src="http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-YYkNq4aUJU4/T9qGUiOSyGI/AAAAAAAAA1o/Y-Gt500Is48/s640/shibacm2.jpg" width="640" /></a></td></tr><tr><td class="tr-caption" style="text-align: center;">vim, and the <a href="http://www.ustream.tv/sfshiba">shiba inu puppy cam</a></td></tr></tbody></table><br />My first larger-scale game project drew to an "official" close last Friday ("official" meaning "It's actually going to be debugged and stuff for the next couple weeks, but for sanity purposes, it's 'done'"). Also last Friday was the end of spring quarter, in which I took a class about empirical research and learned some fundamental but important things like, <i>qualitative research is not meant to be judged on its external validity, but rather it's transferability.</i>&nbsp;The former is the extent to which findings can be "generalized" to the broader world; the latter is the extent to which findings may be found under certain limitations and settings, which have to be defined by the researchers. Subtle.<br /><br />I've also been playing a lot of Diablo 3, despite my deep discomfort with the fact that the only playable dark-skinned character is a witch doctor. Like -- really? <i>Witch doctor?</i>&nbsp;The only playable black person is a spasming, exotified mush of skull masks and voodoo-flavored equips? When this is brought up in conversation circles the immediately following statement always seems to be, <i>But, but the (spoilers) fallen angel of justice is black,</i>&nbsp;as if this suddenly makes witch doctor okay, and I guess it's soothing if what's important is that the games you play be falsely "perfect" enough to not be worth critical analysis.<br /><br />That being said, I'm still enjoying <strike>my social slot machine pinata game</strike> Diablo, though the amount of enjoyment dims a bit into grimacing cynicism every time I find an article about its psychological trickery, <a href="http://www.psychologyofgames.com/2012/06/the-psychology-of-diablo-iii-loot-part-1-anchoring-the-auction-house/">like this one</a>.<br /><br />Since it came out recently, and since my next project (and conceivably all future projects from now on) involve free-to-play games, I've also been playing Nimblebit's recently released Pocket Planes to see what I can glean from its charming pixelated ailerons. &nbsp;In Pocket Planes, you construct your very own airline empire, overseeing the passage of travelers and unusual cargo from city to city.<br /><br /><table align="center" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="tr-caption-container" style="margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto; text-align: center;"><tbody><tr><td style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-HE6RKZhOzew/T-UPXNKS8-I/AAAAAAAABNM/-lXQ2VVwMY0/s1600/photo+(2).PNG" imageanchor="1" style="margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto; text-align: center;"><img border="0" height="425" src="http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-HE6RKZhOzew/T-UPXNKS8-I/AAAAAAAABNM/-lXQ2VVwMY0/s640/photo+(2).PNG" width="640" /></a></td></tr><tr><td class="tr-caption" style="text-align: center;">my plane, named "faire," since the colors seemed kinda fair-like</td></tr></tbody></table><div class="separator" style="clear: both; text-align: left;"><span style="text-align: -webkit-auto;"><br /></span></div><div class="separator" style="clear: both; text-align: left;"><span style="text-align: -webkit-auto;">In particular I was struggling with how I could make an "ecosystem" of goals, something that wouldn't require an endless content feed or "leveling up," some system that could provide its player prodding naturally and grow without much goading and prodding on my part. &nbsp;Something that's nice about Pocket Planes is that, whenever you view the map, you see your "goals:" all those faded-out cities.</span></div><div class="separator" style="clear: both; text-align: left;"><br /></div><div style="text-align: right;"></div><br /><table align="center" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="tr-caption-container" style="margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto; text-align: center;"><tbody><tr><td style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-UOydUvvtrSY/T-UPWVmPETI/AAAAAAAABNE/FO1RT3b_qOk/s1600/photo+(1).PNG" imageanchor="1" style="margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"><img border="0" height="425" src="http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-UOydUvvtrSY/T-UPWVmPETI/AAAAAAAABNE/FO1RT3b_qOk/s640/photo+(1).PNG" width="640" /></a></td></tr><tr><td class="tr-caption" style="text-align: center;">seoul, i will get you soon enough</td></tr></tbody></table><br />I recently tried Kairosoft's recent Epic Astro Story as well, and it had the same sort of carrot-dangling -- faded out areas with rocket ships and caves waiting to explore. In some ways I feel like it's more fun to decide where you want to expand into as well, given the little bit of information. &nbsp;Maybe it's also ~*intrinsic*~, since you know that you're getting <i>something</i>&nbsp;when you expand, but there's still a surprise and mystery concerning what you can do with it.<br /><br /><table align="center" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="tr-caption-container" style="margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto; text-align: center;"><tbody><tr><td style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-2evvfoNGiVM/T-UPX62K-lI/AAAAAAAABNU/6TWOKJeezhw/s1600/photo.PNG" imageanchor="1" style="margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto; text-align: center;"><img border="0" height="400" src="http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-2evvfoNGiVM/T-UPX62K-lI/AAAAAAAABNU/6TWOKJeezhw/s400/photo.PNG" width="266" /></a></td></tr><tr><td class="tr-caption" style="text-align: center;">screenshot of epic astro story, lite version</td></tr></tbody></table><br />Something that I like about both games is that they have warm little cores of personalization/personality. In Pocket Planes, you can color your planes how you like, you can name them, you can outfit their pilots so they have unexpectedly bright facial hair, you can bring the Rosetta Stone from Nagasaki to Sendai, you can bring an ambiguously George Washington-dressed person to Vladivostok. &nbsp;In Epic Astro Story, you have individual citizens with their own names and their own households and preferences. &nbsp;It's the sort of thing that I'm having a hard time finding a parallel for for the amusement park simulation, since amusement parks don't really have little fictional people with natural needs (like work/leisure/exploration) to inhabit them.<br /><br />Recently one of my coworkers admitted that he had never been to Disneyland and was going in the near future, and as soon as people found out they've been taking time to cross vast distances to reach his desk, after which some thirty minutes to an hour will be spent bestowing upon said coworker nostalgic stories and adamant recommendations about Disneyland. &nbsp;"<i>I remember the first time I did X, I felt so [scared/excited/happy]...it's been years now but I really want to go back!"</i>&nbsp;I wish I could capture this sense of excitement, this sort of <i>exuberant memory essence </i>for this amusement park game, but I haven't yet been able to come up with much except perhaps randomly generated events where a little fake visitor will say, "I remember visiting this Fun Bounce in my youth, I love it!"<br /><br />I kind of wish I could visit Disneyland again just to see if inspiration would strike.</div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Off the Leash]]></title>
    <link href="http://neauro.github.io/liwanag/blog/2012/03/21/off-leash/"/>
    <updated>2012-03-21T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://neauro.github.io/liwanag/blog/2012/03/21/off-leash</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
is the cutest dog-based tilt runner game that I've ever played, despite being a game in which it is difficult to play and get a screenshot which captures the excitement of running full tilt (ohoho) with a growing pack of thickly-lined canines. I only wish that there was a shiba inu, but then, I always wish this for everything, even things that don't necessarily include dogs in the first place.<br /><br /><br /><table align="center" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="tr-caption-container" style="margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto; text-align: center;"><tbody><tr><td style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-Mixvu6hl3zE/T2ovQKb4dkI/AAAAAAAAAr8/-lPWr3xePpg/s640/blogger-image-1447569057.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"><img border="0" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-Mixvu6hl3zE/T2ovQKb4dkI/AAAAAAAAAr8/-lPWr3xePpg/s640/blogger-image-1447569057.jpg" /></a></td></tr><tr><td class="tr-caption" style="text-align: center;">screenshot of "off the leash"</td></tr></tbody></table><br />It's free to play, with purchaseable items being more (non-shiba) dogs, power-ups, and even a permanent "2x coin bonus" thing for 99 cents. &nbsp;At some point I unlocked "Tiki Surf Hut Bonus Thing Level" and searched around for it in vain, only to realize that its appearance would be a semi-random in-game&nbsp;occurrence, not something that I could summon at will from the main menu. &nbsp;Was this an example of "verbal, unexpected, informational feedback" that is so beloved of games that hold high the ideal of <a href="http://chrishecker.com/Achievements_Considered_Harmful%3F">instrinsic motivation</a>? &nbsp;Or maybe just UI that wasn't clear enough in informing me that it would reward me with such a bonus level after collecting X amount of steaks and Y number of dalmations during play? &nbsp;The world may never know.<br /><br /><table align="center" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="tr-caption-container" style="margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto; text-align: center;"><tbody><tr><td style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-O6CiUATBERg/T2y5EYdhSiI/AAAAAAAAAsY/EdzBFRxnA_A/s1600/blogger-image-1979466662.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"><img border="0" height="320" src="http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-O6CiUATBERg/T2y5EYdhSiI/AAAAAAAAAsY/EdzBFRxnA_A/s320/blogger-image-1979466662.jpg" width="213" /></a></td></tr><tr><td class="tr-caption" style="text-align: center;">the crash of 38 dogs</td></tr></tbody></table></div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
